[
  {"question": "Guerra - Almighty", "response": "Guerra", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Zodiaco - Almighty", "response": "Zodiaco", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Esclava - Almighty", "response": "Esclava", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Escapate Conmigo - Almighty", "response": "Escapate Conmigo", "artista": "Wisin ft Varios Artistas."},
  {"question": "Sólida - Almighty", "response": "Sólida", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Solita - Almighty Ozuna", "response": "Solita", "artista": "Ozuna ft Almighty, Bad Bunny"},
  {"question": "Vacio - Almighty", "response": "Vacio", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Filipenses - Almighty", "response": "Filipenses", "artista": "Redimi2 Ft. Almighty"},
  {"question": "Khalifa - Almighty Alex Rose", "response": "Khalifa", "artista": "Almighty ft Alex Rose"},
  {"question": "Tu Me Enamoraste - Almighty", "response": "Tu Me Enamoraste", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Varios Artistas"},
  {"question": "Anfetamina Almighty", "response": "Anfetamina", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Luar La L"},
  {"question": "Indiferente - Almighty", "response": "Indiferente", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Asalto - Almighty", "response": "Asalto", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Champion Indiscutible - Almighty", "response": "Champion Indiscutible", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Personalidades - Almighty", "response": "Personalidades", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Farruko"},
  {"question": "Por Si Roncan - Almighty", "response": "Por Si Roncan", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Estrella - El Sica Archivos", "response": "Estrella", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Fendace - Almighty Arcangel", "response": "Fendace", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Almighty"},
  {"question": "Panda - Almighty", "response": "Panda", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Ocho - Almighty", "response": "Ocho", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Invictus - Almighty", "response": "Invictus", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Siempre Está Conmigo - Almighty", "response": "Siempre Está Conmigo", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Mientras Yo Esté Aquí - Almighty", "response": "Mientras Yo Esté Aquí", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Mariscos de Red Lobster - Almighty", "response": "Mariscos de Red Lobster", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "La Nasa - Almighty", "response": "La Nasa", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Timmy Turner - Almighty", "response": "Timmy Turner", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Yo Tengo una Voz - Almighty", "response": "Yo Tengo una Voz", "artista": "El Sica Ft. Almighty"},
  {"question": "Hasta Nunca - Almighty", "response": "Hasta Nunca", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Te Perdi - Almighty", "response": "Te Perdi", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Pusho"},
  {"question": "Tu No Tienes - Almighty", "response": "Tu No Tienes", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Fluye - Almighty", "response": "Fluye", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Por Ti - Almighty Ozuna", "response": "Por Ti", "artista": "Ozuna Ft. Almighty"},
  {"question": "Visita - Almighty", "response": "Visita", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Tu Pelicula - Almighty", "response": "Tu Pelicula", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Meterle - El Sica Archivos", "response": "Meterle", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Poder y Pauta - Almighty", "response": "Poder y Pauta", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Diosa - Almighty", "response": "Diosa", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Moet - Almighty Young", "response": "Moet", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Confiesale - Almighty", "response": "Confiesale", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Illuminatis - Almighty", "response": "Illuminatis", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "TBT - Almighty Ñengo", "response": "TBT", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Te Van a Meter - Almighty", "response": "Te Van a Meter", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Acelerau - Almighty", "response": "Acelerau", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Cuando me Pegue - Almighty", "response": "Cuando me Pegue", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Amarrate las Timber - Almighty Farruko", "response": "Amarrate las Timber", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Farruko"},
  {"question": "Pecados - Almighty", "response": "Pecados", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Abusadora - Almighty", "response": "Abusadora", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Aderall - Almighty", "response": "Aderall", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Recoja - El Sica Archivos", "response": "Recoja", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Costear - Almighty Famouz", "response": "Costear", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Location - Almighty Alex Rose", "response": "Location", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Alex Rose"},
  {"question": "Tu Silueta - Almighty", "response": "Tu Silueta", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Polvo Eterno - Almighty", "response": "Polvo Eterno", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Jon Z"},
  {"question": "Prayer - Almighty Yomo", "response": "Prayer"},
  {"question": "Mayor Que Yo - Wisin y Yandel Pal Mundo", "response": "Mayor Que Yo", "artista": "Wisin Y Yandel"},
  {"question": "No es Nuevo - Almighty", "response": "No es Nuevo", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Haters - Almighty J Alvarez", "response": "Haters", "artista": "J Alvarez Ft. Almighty, Bad Bunny"},
  {"question": "Palestino - Almighty", "response": "Palestino", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Vuele - El Sica Archivos", "response": "Vuele", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Conciencia - Almighty", "response": "Conciencia", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Jon Z"},
  {"question": "Oscar De La Hoya - Almighty", "response": "Oscar De La Hoya", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Jangueo - Almighty", "response": "Jangueo", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Wisin"},
  {"question": "Antes de Lamentar - Almighty", "response": "Antes de Lamentar", "artista": "Almighty Ft. iZaak"},
  {"question": "Por Mas Que Me Amarre - Almighty", "response": "Por Mas Que Me Amarre", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Por Encima - Almighty", "response": "Por Encima", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Tempo"},
  {"question": "Error - Almighty Noriel", "response": "Error", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Noriel"},
  {"question": "Astronauto - Almighty", "response": "Astronauto", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Entre El Bien Y El Mal - Almighty", "response": "Entre El Bien Y El Mal", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Drizmali"},
  {"question": "Llegamos A La Disco - Daddy Yankee", "response": "Llegamos A La Disco", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Varios Artistas"},
  {"question": "No Me Dejes Solo - Daddy Yankee Bonus Track", "response": "No Me Dejes Solo", "artista": "Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Rumbaton - Daddy Yankee Legendaddy", "response": "Rumbaton", "artista": "Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Moviendo Caderas - Daddy Yankee De Lider", "response": "Moviendo Caderas", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Yandel"},
  {"question": "Salud y Vida - Daddy Yankee Barrio Fino", "response": "Salud y Vida", "artista": "Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "El Amante - Daddy Yankee Prestige", "response": "El Amante", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Esto Es Reggaeton Farruko J Alvarez", "response": "Esto Es Reggaeton", "artista": "J Alvarez Ft. Farruko"},
  {"question": "Tu Principe - Daddy Yankee Zion y Lennox", "response": "Tu Principe", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Zion y Lennox"},
  {"question": "La Pregunta - J Alvarez Otro Nivel", "response": "La Pregunta", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Junto al Amanecer - J Alvarez El M", "response": "Junto al Amanecer", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Bella y Sensual - Daddy Yankee Golden", "response": "Bella y Sensual", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Romeo Santos, Nicky Jam"},
  {"question": "La Formula - Daddy Yankee De La Ghetto", "response": "La Formula", "artista": "De La Ghetto Ft. Daddy Yankee, Ozuna"},
  {"question": "Perros Salvajes - Daddy Yankee Prestige", "response": "Perros Salvajes", "artista": "Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Si Supieras - Daddy Yankee S", "response": "Si Supieras", "artista": "Wisin y Yandel Ft. Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Definitivamente - Daddy Yankee Sec", "response": "Definitivamente", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Sech"},
  {"question": "Sexo Sudor y Calor - J Alvarez Otro Nivel", "response": "Sexo Sudor y Calor", "artista": "J Alvarez Ft. Dalmata, Ñejo"},
  {"question": "Regalame una Noche - J Alvarez Arcangerl", "response": "Regalame una Noche", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Una Respuesta - Daddy Yankee", "response": "Una Respuesta", "artista": "Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Rompe Carros - Daddy Yankee", "response": "Rompe Carros", "artista": "Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "La Noche de Los Dos - Daddy Yankee Prestige", "response": "La Noche de Los Dos", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Natalia Jimenez"},
  {"question": "Estas Aqui - Daddy Yankee Mi Historia", "response": "Estas Aqui", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft Nicky Jam"},
  {"question": "Se Acabó el Amor - J Alvarez Top", "response": "Se Acabó el Amor", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "No Sabe Mentir - J Alvarez", "response": "No Sabe Mentir", "artista": "J Alvarez Ft. Luigi 21 Plus"},
  {"question": "Se Acabó - J Alvarez Mek", "response": "Se Acabó", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Actúa - J Alvarez Nazza", "response": "Actúa", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Nada es Eterno - J Alvarez", "response": "Nada es Eterno", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Tentandome - J Alvarez Wave", "response": "Tentandome", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "La Temperatura - J Alvarez", "response": "La Temperatura", "artista": "J Alvarez"},
  {"question": "Guaya - Daddy Yankee Nazza", "response": "Guaya", "artista": "Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Po Encima - Arcangel", "response": "Po Encima", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Bryan Myers"},
  {"question": "Camuflaje - Arcangel", "response": "Camuflaje", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Alexis y Fido"},
  {"question": "Me Prefieres a Mi - Arcangel N", "response": "Me Prefieres a Mi", "artista": "Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Amigos y Enemigos - Almighty", "response": "Amigos y Enemigos", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Noriel, Bad Bunny"},
  {"question": "Como Tiene Que Ser - Arcangel", "response": "Como Tiene Que Ser", "artista": "Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Mas Que Ayer - Arcangel", "response": "Mas Que Ayer", "artista": "Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Hace Mucho Tiempo - Arcangel w", "response": "Hace Mucho Tiempo", "artista": "Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Te Robo - Arcangel", "response": "Te Robo", "artista": "Arcangel Ft De La Ghetto"},
  {"question": "Sola - Arcangel Sentimiento", "response": "Sola", "artista": "Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Mala Conducta - Arcangel", "response": "Mala Conducta", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Alexis y Fido"},
  {"question": "Para Que Volver - Arcangel Jadiel", "response": "Para Que Volver", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Jadiel"},
  {"question": "La Loca - Arcangel Jory", "response": "La Loca", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Jory"},
  {"question": "Una Oportunidad - El Sica Kendo", "response": "Una Oportunidad", "artista": "El Sica Ft. Kendo Kaponi"},
  {"question": "Pal Muro - Arcangel Alexio", "response": "Pal Muro", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Alexio La Bestia"},
  {"question": "Pasión - Daddy Yankee Arcangel", "response": "Pasión", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Pakas de 100 - Daddy Yankee Arcangel", "response": "Pakas de 100", "artista": "Daddy Yankee Ft. Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Si Tu No Estas - Nicky Jam De La Ghett", "response": "Si Tu No Estas", "artista": "Nicky Jam Ft. De La Ghetto"},
  {"question": "Soltera - Arcangel Farruko", "response": "Soltera", "artista": "Arcangel Ft. Farruko"},
  {"question": "Mia - Almighty Custom", "response": "Mia", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Por Ella - Almighty", "response": "Por Ella", "artista": "Almighty"},
  {"question": "Si Se Da - Myke Towers Remix", "response": "Si Se Da", "artista": "Myke Towers"},
  {"question": "China - Anuel Daddy Yankee n", "response": "China", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Quiere Beber - Anuel real", "response": "Quiere Beber", "artista": "Anuel"},
  {"question": "Volver - El Sica Archivos", "response": "Volver", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Delincuente - Anuel Tokischa", "response": "Delincuente", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Tokischa, Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Delincuente - Anuel Farruko Gangalee", "response": "Delincuente", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Farruko"},
  {"question": "Sola - Anuel nw", "response": "Sola", "artista": "Anuel"},
  {"question": "Ver Amor - El Sica", "response": "Ver Amor", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Ayer - Anuel Dj Nelson", "response": "Ayer", "artista": "Anuel"},
  {"question": "To Te Llueve - El Sica", "response": "To Te Llueve", "artista": "El Sica Ft. Arcangel, De La Ghetto"},
  {"question": "Mas Rica Que Ayer - Anuel AA Mambo Kin", "response": "Mas Rica Que Ayer", "artista": "Anuel"},
  {"question": "Toki - Anuel AA Casper Luar", "response": "Toki", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Luar La L, Casper"},
  {"question": "Tacos Gucci - Anuel AA", "response": "Tacos Gucci", "artista": "Anuel"},
  {"question": "Jangueo - Anuel Tego", "response": "Jangueo", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Tego Calderon"},
  {"question": "Las Jordan - Anuel", "response": "Las Jordan", "artista": "Anuel"},
  {"question": "Medusa - Anuel Jhayco", "response": "Medusa", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Jhayco"},
  {"question": "Ella y Yo - Anuel Farruko Almighty", "response": "Ella y Yo", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Almighty, Farruko, Tempo"},
  {"question": "Na Nuevo - Anuel AA", "response": "Na Nuevo", "artista": "Anuel"},
  {"question": "Nacimos Pa Morir - Anuel AA Jory", "response": "Nacimos Pa Morir", "artista": "Anuel Ft. Jory"},
  {"question": "Tanto Tiempo - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "Tanto Tiempo", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus Ft. Arcangel"},
  {"question": "No Sabe Mentir - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "No Sabe Mentir", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus"},
  {"question": "Dos Clases de Mujeres - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "Dos Clases de Mujeres", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus"},
  {"question": "No Te Voy a Mentir - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "No Te Voy a Mentir", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus"},
  {"question": "Esto Se Jodio - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "Esto Se Jodio", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus"},
  {"question": "Mala Influencia - Luigi 21 Plus Farruko", "response": "Mala Influencia", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus Ft. Farruko"},
  {"question": "Solteria - Luigi 21 Plus Arcangel", "response": "Solteria", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus Ft. Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Todas En Fila - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "Todas En Fila", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus Ft. De La Ghetto, Ozuna, Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Dulce pa Las Babys - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "Dulce pa Las Babys", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus"},
  {"question": "Ninguno esta aqui - El Sica almighty", "response": "Ninguno Esta Aqui", "artista": "El Sica Ft. Almighty"},
  {"question": "Bailen - Luigi 21 Plus", "response": "Bailen", "artista": "Luigi 21 Plus Ft. Varios Artistas"},
  {"question": "Me Elevas a las Nubes - Juanka", "response": "Me Elevas a las Nubes", "artista": "Juanka"},
  {"question": "La Jeepeta remix - Nio Garcia", "response": "La Jeepeta remix", "artista": "Nio Garcia"},
  {"question": "En el Corazon Nadie Manda - Juanka", "response": "En el Corazon Nadie Manda", "artista": "Juanka"},
  {"question": "Esperando Por Ti - Juanka", "response": "Esperando Por Ti", "artista": "Juanka"},
  {"question": "No Quiere Ceder - El Sica", "response": "No Quiere Ceder", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Cuando Quieras Volver - Juanka", "response": "Cuando Quieras Volver", "artista": "Juanka"},
  {"question": "Cuando Se Apague La Luz - Juanka", "response": "Cuando Se Apague La Luz", "artista": "Juanka"},
  {"question": "Besos en Guerra - Morat Juanes", "response": "Besos en Guerra", "artista": "Morat Ft. Juanes"},
  {"question": "Stupid Love Story - Canserbero", "response": "Stupid Love Story", "artista": "Canserbero"},
  {"question": "Jeremias - Canserbero Muerte", "response": "Jeremias", "artista": "Canserbero"},
  {"question": "Volviendome Loco - El Sica", "response": "Volviendome Loco", "artista": "El Sica"},
  {"question": "Pensando en Ti - Canserbero Vida", "response": "Pensando en Ti", "artista": "Canserbero"},
  {"question": "Stop - Canserbero Apache", "response": "Stop", "artista": "Canserbero Ft. Apache"},
  {"question": "Es Epico - Canserbero Muerte E", "response": "Es Epico", "artista": "Canserbero"},
  {"question": "Tu Turrito - Callejero Fino", "response": "Tu Turrito", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Mata - Callejero Fino", "response": "Mata", "artista": "Callajero Fino"},
  {"question": "Suelta - Callejero Finox", "response": "Suelta", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Paris - Duki Moratx", "response": "Paris", "artista": "Duki Ft. Morat"},
  {"question": "No Me Llores - Dukix", "response": "No Me Llores", "artista": "Duki"},
  {"question": "Panamá - Duki Truenox", "response": "Panamá", "artista": "Duki ft. Trueno"},
  {"question": "Pintao - Dukix", "response": "Pintao", "artista": "Duki"},
  {"question": "AMIRI - Soy Turista", "response": "AMIRI", "artista": "Soy Turista"},
  {"question": "Malas Intenciones - Soy Turista", "response": "Malas Intenciones", "artista": "Soy Turista"},
  {"question": "CERO$ - Callejero Finox", "response": "CERO$", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Culo - Callejero Finox", "response": "Culo", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "PA LAS LOCAS - Callejero Fino", "response": "PA LAS LOCAS", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Traidora - Callejero Fino", "response": "Traidora", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Bastardo - Ñengo Flow", "response": "Bastardo", "artista": "Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Escándalo - Ñengo Flowx", "response": "Escándalo", "artista": "Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Cuando Me Dirá - Ñengo Flowx", "response": "Cuando Me Dirá", "artista": "Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Mia - Ñengo Flow Darellx", "response": "Mia", "artista": "Ñengo Flow Ft. Darell"},
  {"question": "No Dice Na - Ñengo Flowx", "response": "No Dice Na", "artista": "Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Devórame - Ñengo Flowx", "response": "Devórame", "artista": "Ñengo Flow Ft. Arcangel"},
  {"question": "Me Niegas - Baby Rasta y Gringo Ñengo Flowx", "response": "Me Niegas", "artista": "Baby Rasta y Gringo Ft. Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Sigue Viajando - Ñengo Flowx", "response": "Sigue Viajando", "artista": "Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Traicionera - Ñengo Flowx", "response": "Traicionera", "artista": "Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Titan - Callejero Finofi", "response": "Titan", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Fua Mi Amor - Callejero Fino", "response": "Fua Mi Amor", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Que te Vaya Bien - Callejero Fino", "response": "Que te Vaya Bien", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Le Doy Perreo - Callejero Finox", "response": "Le Doy Perreo", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Pide - Callejero Fino", "response": "Pide", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "ATR - Callejero Finox", "response": "ATR", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "Tus Vueltas - Milo Jx", "response": "Tus Vueltas", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "FLA - Milo Jx", "response": "FLA", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Al Sol - Milo Jx", "response": "Al Sol", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Porciento - Almighty Kele", "response": "Porciento", "artista": "Almighty Ft. Kele"},
  {"question": "No Mucho - Milo Jx", "response": "No Mucho", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Bandolero - Don Omar Tego Calderon Fast", "response": "Bandolero", "artista": "Don Omar Ft. Tego Calderon"},
  {"question": "Salio El Sol - Don Omar Remastered", "response": "Salio El Sol", "artista": "Don Omar"},
  {"question": "Virtual Diva - Don Omar Fast", "response": "Virtual Diva", "artista": "Don Omar"},
  {"question": "Mirame Una Vez Mas - Nestor en Bloque Rom", "response": "Mirame Una Vez Mas", "artista": "Nestor En Bloque"},
  {"question": "Te Busco - Cosculluela Nickyx", "response": "Te Busco", "artista": "Cosculluela Ft. Nicky Jam"},
  {"question": "DM - Cosculluelax", "response": "DM", "artista": "Cosculluela"},
  {"question": "Lloras - Plan Bx", "response": "Lloras", "artista": "Plan B"},
  {"question": "Besame - Milo J Tiago Khea Neo Pistea Seven", "response": "Besame", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Fruto - Milo Jx", "response": "Fruto", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "No Soy Eterno - Milo J en dormir sin madrid w", "response": "No Soy Eterno", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Al Borde - Milo J x", "response": "Al Borde", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Me Gustaria - Sayian Jimmyx", "response": "Me Gustaria", "artista": "Sayian Jimmy"},
  {"question": "Noche De Colores - Sayian Jimmyx", "response": "Noche De Colores", "artista": "Sayian Jimmy"},
  {"question": "Mi Fanatica - Sayian Jimmyx", "response": "Mi Fanatica", "artista": "Sayian Jimmy"},
  {"question": "Bien Loco - Nova Y Joryx a", "response": "Bien Loco", "artista": "Nova y Jory"},
  {"question": "Ay Parcera - Nickoog Clk", "response": "Ay Parcera", "artista": "Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "Humo - Nickoog Clkx", "response": "Humo", "artista": "Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "Chamaka - Nickoog Clk x", "response": "Chamaka", "artista": "Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "Por Ella - Nickoog Clk x", "response": "Por Ella", "artista": "Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "Tu Flaite - Nickoog Clk x", "response": "Tu Flaite", "artista": "Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "Que Se Hace - Nickoog Clk x", "response": "Que Se Hace", "artista": "Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "Perreo Del Futuro - Nickoog Clk x", "response": "Perreo Del Futuro", "artista": "Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "Mi Gata - Standly El Barto ly", "response": "Mi Gata", "artista": "Standly"},
  {"question": "Chica De Museo - Standly", "response": "Chica De Museo", "artista": "Standly"},
  {"question": "Bailemos Reggaeton - Standly x", "response": "Bailemos Reggaeton", "artista": "Standly"},
  {"question": "Me Ama Me Odia - Ozunax", "response": "Me Ama Me Odia", "artista": "Ozuna"},
  {"question": "Rincon - Milo J Ric", "response": "Rincon", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Adios, Amor Adios - Nestor en Bloque Rom", "response": "Adios, Amor Adios", "artista": "Nestor En Bloque"},
  {"question": "Mi Promesa - Nestor en Bloque unico", "response": "Mi Promesa", "artista": "Nestor En Bloque"},
  {"question": "Flotao - Sayian Jimmyx", "response": "Flotao", "artista": "Sayian Jimmy"},
  {"question": "Pa Pegarme - Sayian Jimmyx", "response": "Pa Pegarme", "artista": "Sayian Jimmy"},
  {"question": "La Coste - Sayian Jimmyx", "response": "La Coste", "artista": "Sayian Jimmy"},
  {"question": "Amor Verdadero - Sayian Jimmyx", "response": "Amor Verdadero", "artista": "Sayian Jimmy"},
  {"question": "Morocha - Milo Jx", "response": "Morocha", "artista": "Milo J"},
  {"question": "Pretextos - Cosculluela Malumax", "response": "Pretextos", "artista": "Cosculluela ft. Maluma"},
  {"question": "23 - Cosculluela Anuel", "response": "23", "artista": "Cosculluela Ft. Anuel"},
  {"question": "La Boda - Cosculluela Kendo O'neill", "response": "La Boda", "artista": "Cosculluela Ft. Kendo Kaponi"},
  {"question": "LATI2 - Callejero Fino", "response": "LATI2", "artista": "Callejero Fino"},
  {"question": "ANDO - Jere Klein gitto be", "response": "ANDO", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "KE MAL - Jere Kleinx", "response": "KE MAL", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "LOCA FARANDULERA - Jere Kleinx", "response": "LOCA FARANDULERA", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "24/7 - Jere Klein", "response": "24/7", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "YIMMY - Jere Klein", "response": "YIMMY", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "ANDAMOS READY - Jere KleinX", "response": "ANDAMOS READY", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "XQ TAN SOLA? - Jere Klein Nicko", "response": "XQ TAN SOLA?", "artista": "Jere Klein Ft. Nickoog Clk"},
  {"question": "UNA EN UN MILLON - Jere KleinX", "response": "UNA EN UN MILLON", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "Ya No Pienso En Ti - Jere Kleinx", "response": "Ya No Pienso En Ti", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "Mi Fanatica - Jere Kleinx", "response": "Mi Fanatica", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "Traketo - Jere Klein", "response": "Traketo", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "Rockstar - Dukixa", "response": "Rockstar", "artista": "Duki"},
  {"question": "Rockstar - Jere Kleinxx", "response": "Rockstar", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "Ibiza - Jere Kleinx", "response": "Ibiza", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "38 - Jere Kleinx", "response": "38", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "Mujer Fina - Jere Klein", "response": "Mujer Fina", "artista": "Jere Klein"},
  {"question": "DISCOTEKA - The La Planta BM", "response": "DISCOTEKA", "artista": "The La Planta"},
  {"question": "Cabaña - Jordan 23x", "response": "Cabaña", "artista": "El Jordan 23"},
  {"question": "Bailando - El Jordan 23 Standlyx", "response": "Bailando", "artista": "El Jordan 23"},
  {"question": "Candy - Plan Bx", "response": "Candy", "artista": "Plan B"},
  {"question": "Fanatica Sensual - Plan Bx", "response": "Fanatica Sensual", "artista": "Plan B"},
  {"question": "Choca - Plan Bx", "response": "Choca", "artista": "Plan B"},
  {"question": "Ella Fuma - Plan Bx", "response": "Ella Fuma", "artista": "Plan B"},
  {"question": "Ella Se Contradice - Baby Rasta y Gringox", "response": "Ella Se Contradice", "artista": "Baby Rasta y Gringo"},
  {"question": "Zapatito Roto - Plan B Tego", "response": "Zapatito Roto", "artista": "Plan B ft. Tego Calderon"},
  {"question": "Nos Fuimos Discoteca - Plan B x", "response": "Nos Fuimos Discoteca", "artista": "Plan B"},
  {"question": "A Donde Voy - Cosculluela Daddy Yankee", "response": "A Donde Voy", "artista": "Cosculluela Ft. Daddy Yankee"},
  {"question": "Baby Boo - Cosculluelax", "response": "Baby Boo", "artista": "Cosculluela"},
  {"question": "Dime a Ver - Cosculluelax", "response": "Dime a Ver", "artista": "Cosculluela"},
  {"question": "0 Sentimientos - Jon Z Noriel Darkiel Lyan", "response": "0 Sentimientos", "artista": "Jon Z Ft. Varios Artistas"},
  {"question": "Prefiere Estar Sola - Baby Rasta Ñengo Flow", "response": "Prefiere Estar Sola", "artista": "Baby Rasta Ft. Ñengo Flow"},
  {"question": "Diabolica - Dei V Chris Mj", "response": "Diabolica", "artista": "Dei V"},
  {"question": "Gatita Gangster - Dei V", "response": "Gatita Gangster", "artista": "Dei V"},
  {"question": "Pacto - Jay Wheeler Anuelx", "response": "Pacto", "artista": "Jay Wheeler Ft. Anuel AA"},
  {"question": "Single - Dei Vx", "response": "Single", "artista": "Dei V"},
  {"question": "La Esquina - Juanka Dei V", "response": "La Esquina", "artista": "Juanka Ft. Dei V"},
  {"question": "Baby Girl - De La Ghetto Dei V", "response": "Baby Girl", "artista": "De La Ghetto Ft. Dei V"},
  {"question": "Los Que Son - Dei V YOVNGCHIMI Chris", "response": "Los Que Son", "artista": "Dei V Ft. Yovngchimi"}
]